Boston Streets Collection MS102
Tufts Archival Research Center
- Images, unbound, 1762 -- 1980; MS102.001; 409 Digital Object(s)
  - 31 Bromfield Street, 1923-11-17; MS102.001.DO.00243; Globe Newspaper Co.
    Massachusetts; Boston (Mass.); Washington Street Shopping District; Bromfield Street; Province Street; Buildings; Commercial buildings; Businesses; Stores, retail; Commercial products; Signs and signboards; Automobiles; Construction equipment; Justice, Charles H.; Sumner's Market Company; Camera Hospital
  - Houses on Bulfinch Street, July, 1961-07-01; MS102.001.DO.00244; Unknown
    Massachusetts; Boston (Mass.); Government Center; Bulfinch Street; Buildings; Dwellings; Houses
  - Bulfinch Place Unitarian Church, July, 1961-07-01; MS102.001.DO.00245; Unknown
    Massachusetts; Boston (Mass.); Government Center; Bulfinch Street; Bulfinch Place; Buildings; Churches; Bulfinch Place Church; People; Men; Construction equipment; Bulfinch Place Unitarian Church
  - A demolition site on Bulfinch Street across from the Bulfinch Place Unitarian Church, July, 1961-07-01; MS102.001.DO.00246; Unknown
    Massachusetts; Boston (Mass.); Government Center; Bulfinch Street; Bulfinch Place; Building sites; Buildings-Repair and reconstruction; Apartment houses; Churches; Bulfinch Place Church; Automobiles; Bulfinch Place Unitarian Church
  - House of Jonathan Howard, 1874 -- 1898; MS102.001.DO.00247; Unknown
    Massachusetts; Boston (Mass.); Government Center; Bulfinch Street; Bulfinch Place; Buildings; Dwellings; Houses; Signs and signboards; Street-lighting; Howard, Jonathan
  - View of a building site from Bowdoin and Allston Streets, May, 1961-05-01; MS102.001.DO.00248; Unknown
    Massachusetts; Boston (Mass.); Beacon Hill (Mass.); Allston Street; Bowdoin Street; Buildings; Dwellings; Houses; Apartment houses; Building sites
  - Boston Board of Trade Building, 1898 -- 1915; MS102.001.DO.00249; Unknown
    Massachusetts; Boston (Mass.); Custom House District; Broad Street; State Street; Buildings; Commercial buildings; Office buildings; Businesses; Stores, retail; Dwellings; Apartment houses; People; Pedestrians; Horse-drawn vehicles; Wagons; Carriages and carts; Signs and signboards; Vieira, Manuel; Huntress, R.W.; Manuel Vieira Cigars
  - Bromfield Street, 1859; MS102.001.DO.00250; Seaver, Chandler Jr.
    Massachusetts; Boston (Mass.); Washington Street; Bromfield Street; Buildings; Commercial buildings; Businesses; Stores, retail; Hotels; Churches; Second Methodist Episcopal Church; Horse-drawn vehicles; Wagons; Trolley buses; Signs and signboards; Awnings; Edwards, Pierpont; Raymond, Freeman C.; Bromfield House; P. Edwards and Company; Second Methodist Episcopal Church
  - Cambridge Street widening, 1926; MS102.001.DO.00251; Unknown
    Massachusetts; Boston (Mass.); Beacon Hill (Mass.); Cambridge Street; Buildings; Building sites; Parkman Market; Jails; Suffolk County Jail; Charles Street Jail; Cupolas; Street-lighting; Pedestrians; Automobiles; Street-railroads--track; Electric lines, poles and towers
  - Partially demolished building at the corner of Cambridge and Bowdoin Streets, 1926; MS102.001.DO.00252; Unknown
    Massachusetts; Boston (Mass.); Government Center; Cambridge Street; Buildings; Building sites; Pedestrians; Electric lines, poles and towers; Street-railroads--track
  - State Health, Education and Welfare Service Center and the Old West Church, 1974; MS102.001.DO.00253; Weaver, David
    Massachusetts; Boston (Mass.); Government Center; Cambridge Street; New Chardon; Buildings; Government buildings; State Health, Education and Welfare Service Center; Churches; Old West Church; Automobiles; Street-lighting; Building sites; Rudolph, Paul; Dyer, M. A.; Shepley, Bulfinch, Richardson and Abbott; Pedersen and Tilney; Desmond and Lord, Inc.
  - Cambridge Street widening, 1926; MS102.001.DO.00254; Unknown
    Massachusetts; Boston (Mass.); Beacon Hill (Mass.); Cambridge Street; Buildings; Building sites; Streets; People; Pedestrians; Laborers; Automobiles; Signs and signboards; Street-railroads--track; Whitcomb, William H.; W.H. Whitcomb Construction Company
  - Cambridge Street, 1950; MS102.001.DO.00255; Neiley, Robert
    Massachusetts; Boston (Mass.); Beacon Hill (Mass.); Cambridge Street; Buildings; Commercial buildings; Businesses; Stores, retail; Restaurants, lunch rooms, etc.; Service stations; Signs and signboards; Pedestrians; Automobiles; Trucks, automobile; Stop and Shop; Hancock Spa; White Rose Coffee Shop; Simmons Package Store, Inc.; Amoco Gas; Mitchell's Lunch
  - Cambridge Street between the corner of Irving Street and Bowdoin Square, 1950; MS102.001.DO.00256; Neiley, Robert
    Massachusetts; Boston (Mass.); Beacon Hill (Mass.); Cambridge Street; Buildings; Commercial buildings; Businesses; Stores, retail; Restaurants, lunch rooms, etc.; Grocers; Dry cleaning; Public utilities; Signs and signboards; Automobiles; Pedestrians; Cupolas; Street-lighting; West End Branch of the Boston Public Library; Kleen Rite Cleaners; Mitchell's Lunch; Stop and Shop; New England Telephone and Telegraph Company
  - Fire station on Cambridge Street, July, 1961-07-01; MS102.001.DO.00257; Unknown
    Massachusetts; Boston (Mass.); Cambridge Street; Buildings; Municipal buildings; Fire stations; People; Men; City of Boston Fire Department
  - Suffolk County Jail, 1851 -- 1860; MS102.001.DO.00258; Soule, John P.
    Massachusetts; Boston (Mass.); Beacon Hill (Mass.); Charles Street; Cambridge Street; Buildings; Municipal buildings; Jails; Suffolk County Jail; Charles Street Jail
  - Cambridge Street between Bowdoin and Scollay Square, 1955; MS102.001.DO.00259; Neiley, Robert
    Massachusetts; Boston (Mass.); Government Center; Cambridge Street; Scollay Square; Buildings; Commercial buildings; Businesses; Stores, retail; Restaurants, lunch rooms, etc.; Signs and signboards; Pedestrians; Automobiles; Trucks, automobile; Squares (open spaces); Government buildings; Customhouses; Custom House; Ciampa, John B.; Goldman, Phillip; Goldman, Rouben; Belmont House; Ferrara's Restaurant and Sea Grill; Bowdoin Square Cafe; Royal Cafe; Goldman's Clothes Shop
  - Widening of Cambridge Street from Scollay Square to just southwest of Bowdoin Square, 1926; MS102.001.DO.00260; Unknown
    Massachusetts; Boston (Mass.); Government Center; Cambridge Street; Buildings; Building sites; Streets; Pedestrians; Automobiles; Trucks, automobile; Horse-drawn vehicles; Wagons; Awnings; Signs and signboards; Street-lighting; Street-railroads--track
  - Parkman Building cupola, n.d., MS102.001.DO.00261; Globe Newspaper Co.
    Massachusetts; Boston (Mass.); Beacon Hill (Mass.); Cambridge Street; North Grove Street; Cupolas
  - Old West Church, 1837 -- 1887; MS102.001.DO.00262; Unknown
    Massachusetts; Boston (Mass.); Beacon Hill (Mass.); Cambridge Street; Lowell Square; Buildings; Churches; Old West Church; Clocks and watches; Towers; Fences; Fountains; Squares (open spaces); Benjamin, Asher; Bartol, Dr. Cyrus; Old West Church, United Methodist
  - Old West Church, 1860 -- 1890; MS102.001.DO.00263; Alden, A. E.
    Massachusetts; Boston (Mass.); Beacon Hill (Mass.); Cambridge Street; Lowell Square; Buildings; Churches; Old West Church; Fences; Squares (open spaces); Clocks and watches; Towers; Railroads-track; Benjamin, Asher; Old West Church, United Methodist
  - West End Branch of the Boston Public Library, 1894 -- 1920; MS102.001.DO.00264; Unknown
    Massachusetts; Boston (Mass.); Beacon Hill (Mass.); Cambridge Street; Lynde Street; Lowell Square; Buildings; Libraries; West End Branch of the Boston Public Library; Towers; Clocks and watches; Fences; Fountains; Squares (open spaces); Benjamin, Asher; Boston Public Library
  - Old West Chruch, 1885 -- 1894; MS102.001.DO.00265; Unknown
    Massachusetts; Boston (Mass.); Beacon Hill (Mass.); Cambridge Street; Lynde Street; Lowell Square; Buildings; Churches; Old West Church; Towers; Clocks and watches; Fences; Squares (open spaces); Street-lighting; Benjamin, Asher; Old West Church, United Methodist
  - Old West Chruch, 1885 -- 1894; MS102.001.DO.00266; Unknown
  - Harrison Gray Otis house and the Old West Church, 1916; MS102.001.DO.00267; Frank Causins Art Company
    Massachusetts; Boston (Mass.); Beacon Hill (Mass.); Cambridge Street; Lynde Street; Buildings; Dwellings; Houses; Libraries; West End Branch of the Boston Public Library; Commercial buildings; Businesses; Stores, retail; Laundries; Painters; Boots and shoes-repairing; People; Men; Children; Fences; Clocks and watches; Railroads-track; Otis, Harrison Gray; Bulfinch, Charles; Benjamin, Asher; Wells, J.B.; Boston Public Library; C. Lee Laundry; Boot and Shoe Repairing
  - First Harrison Gray Otis house at 141 Cambridge Street, 1961; MS102.001.DO.00268; Woodman, W.C.
    Massachusetts; Boston (Mass.); Beacon Hill (Mass.); Cambridge Street; Lynde Street; Buildings; Dwellings; Houses; Signs and signboards; Fences; Gates; Otis, Harrison Gray; Bulfinch, Charles; Society for the Preservation of New England Antiquities (SPNEA)
  - Lynde Street entrance to the Harrison Gray Otis House, 1890 -- 1916; MS102.001.DO.00269; Frank Causins Art Company
    Massachusetts; Boston (Mass.); Beacon Hill (Mass.); Cambridge Street; Lynde Street; Buildings; Dwellings; Apartment houses; Houses; Signs and signboards; Doors; Businesses; Stores, retail; Otis, Harrison Gray; Bulfinch, Charles
  - Front door of the Harrison Gray Otis house at 2 Lynde Street, 1890 -- 1916; MS102.001.DO.00270; Frank Causins Art Company
    Massachusetts; Boston (Mass.); Beacon Hill (Mass.); Lynde Street; Cambridge Street; Doors; Bulfinch, Charles; Otis, Harrison Gray
  - Boston elevated railway at the corner of Canal and Causway Streets, July, 1961-07-01; MS102.001.DO.00271; Unknown
    Massachusetts; Boston (Mass.); Canal Street; Causeway Street; Buildings; Railroad stations; North Station; Signs and signboards; Elevated railroads; Automobiles; Trucks, automobile; Pedestrians; Home Hamburgers; Metropolitan Transit Authority
  - North Station from Canal Street, 1961-07-12; MS102.001.DO.00272; Unknown
    Massachusetts; Boston (Mass.); Canal Street; Causeway Street; Buildings; Commercial buildings; Businesses; Stores, retail; Restaurants, lunch rooms, etc.; Railroad stations; North Station; Automobiles; Trucks, automobile; Parking meters; Macy's Liquors; Hayes-Bickford Lunch System, Inc.; Metropolitan Transit Authority
  - Corner of Canal and Merrimac Streets, 1933; MS102.001.DO.00273; Globe Newspaper Co.
    Massachusetts; Boston (Mass.); Government Center; Merrimac Street; Canal Street; Haymarket Square; Buildings; Building sites; Commercial buildings; Municipal buildings; City Scales; Signs and signboards; Pedestrians; Automobiles; Railroads-track; Whitehead, Walter; Mason, Frank L.; Leavens and Company (William Leavens and Company, Inc.); Boston Inspectional Services, Division of Weights and Measures
  - 36-38 Carver Street during the widening of Stuart Street, 1920; MS102.001.DO.00274; Unknown
    Massachusetts; Boston (Mass.); Theater District; Carver Street; Eliot Street; Buildings; Dwellings; Houses; Commercial buildings; Businesses; Stores, retail; Parking garages; People; Men; Horse-drawn vehicles; Wagons; Automobiles; Dodge, Charles A.; C.C. Dodge Company; Eliot Street Garage Company
  - Stuart Street, 1929; MS102.001.DO.00275; Unknown
    Massachusetts; Boston (Mass.); Theater District; Stuart Street; Eliot Street; Carver Street; Buildings; Dwellings; Houses; Commercial buildings; Businesses; Stores, retail; Parking garages; Theaters; Plymouth Theater; Automobiles; Signs and signboards; Eliot Street Garage Company; Plymouth Theater
  - 62 Carver Street, 1933; MS102.001.DO.00276; George E. Lawrence Company
    Massachusetts; Boston (Mass.); Theater District; Carver Street; Buildings; Dwellings; Houses; Automobiles; Haviland, Henry
  - Harvard Bridge during a storm, December, 1909-12-01; MS102.001.DO.00277; Unknown
    Massachusetts; Boston (Mass.); Cambridge (Mass.); Back Bay (Mass.); Massachusetts Avenue; Bridges; Harvard Bridge; Horse-drawn vehicles; Carriages and carts; Trolley buses; Rivers; Charles River
  - Longfellow Bridge, 1907; MS102.001.DO.00278; Unknown
    Massachusetts; Boston (Mass.); Beacon Hill (Mass.); Cambridge (Mass.); Cambridge Street; Bridges; Longfellow Bridge; Towers; Street-lighting; Rivers; Charles River; Buildings; Public utilities; Wheelwright, Edmund March; Boston Gaslighting Company
  - State House, Beacon Street, n.d., MS102.001.DO.00279; Unknown
    Massachusetts; Boston (Mass.); Beacon Hill (Mass.); Beacon Street
  - West End Bridge and construction of the Longfellow Bridge, 1907; MS102.001.DO.00280
    Massachusetts; Boston (Mass.); Cambridge (Mass.); Cambridge Street; Buildings; Longfellow Bridge; West End Bridge; Building sites; Street-lighting; Electric lines, poles and towers; Horse-drawn vehicles; Pedestrians; Wheelwright, Edmund March
  - Harvard Bridge after a storm, December, 1909-12-01; MS102.001.DO.00281; Unknown
    Massachusetts; Boston (Mass.); Back Bay (Mass.); Cambridge (Mass.); Massachusetts Avenue; Bridges; Harvard Bridge; Electric lines, poles and towers; Trolley buses; Horse-drawn vehicles; Wagons; Snow; Rivers; Charles River
  - Longfellow Bridge, 1910; MS102.001.DO.00282; Unknown
    Massachusetts; Boston (Mass.); Cambridge (Mass.); Cambridge Street; Embankment Road; Bridges; Longfellow Bridge; Open spaces; Charles River Embankment; Street-lighting; Automobiles; Towers; Pedestrians; Rivers; Charles River; Wheelwright, Edmund March
  - Harvard Stadium, 1910; MS102.001.DO.00283; Unknown
    Massachusetts; Boston (Mass.); Cambridge (Mass.); Allston-Brighton (Mass.); Sports buildings; Athletic fields; Harvard Stadium (Soldiers Field); Bridges; Rivers; Charles River; Horse-drawn vehicles; Wagons; Automobiles; Buildings; Dwellings; Houses; Electric lines, poles and towers; Harvard University
  - Longfellow Bridge, 1910; MS102.001.DO.00284; Unknown
    Massachusetts; Boston (Mass.); Cambridge (Mass.); Cambridge Street; Bridges; Longfellow Bridge; Rivers; Charles River; Street-lighting; Towers; Wheelwright, Edmund March
  - Longfellow Bridge, 1913; MS102.001.DO.00285; Unknown
    Massachusetts; Boston (Mass.); Cambridge (Mass.); Cambridge Street; Bridges; Longfellow Bridge; Harvard Bridge; Rivers; Charles River; Street-lighting; Horse-drawn vehicles; Wagons; Carriages and carts; Trolley buses; Elevated railroads; Towers; People; Children; Parks; Charlesbank; Wheelwright, Edmund March; Olmsted, Frederick Law; Rawson and Morrison MFG. Co.
  - West End Bridge, 1907; MS102.001.DO.00286; Unknown
    Massachusetts; Boston (Mass.); Cambridge (Mass.); Cambridge Street; Buildings; Factories; Smokestacks; Piers; Bridges; West End Bridge; Pedestrians; Trolley buses; Rivers; Charles River; Rawson and Morrison MFG. Co.; Edward Kendall and Sons; Charles River Ironworks
  - Storrow Drive, 1950; MS102.001.DO.00287; Unknown
    Massachusetts; Boston (Mass.); Back Bay (Mass.); The Esplanade; Storrow Drive; Streets; Buildings; Dwellings; Houses; Parks; The Esplanade; Bridges; Harvard Bridge; Street-lighting; Automobiles; Storrow, James J.
  - Construction of the Hatch Memorial Shell, 1940; MS102.001.DO.00288; Snow, Edward R.
    Massachusetts; Boston (Mass.); The Esplanade; Building sites; Stages; Hatch Memorial Shell; People; Laborers
  - Promenaders strolling along the Charles River Embankment in Back Bay, 1912; MS102.001.DO.00289; Unknown
    Massachusetts; Boston (Mass.); Back Bay (Mass.); Beacon Street; People; Pedestrians; Men; Women; Street-lighting; Rivers; Charles River; Buildings; Dwellings; Houses; Charles River Embankment
  - Charles River Basin, 1940; MS102.001.DO.00290; Scott, Rovere
    Massachusetts; Boston (Mass.); Back Bay (Mass.); The Esplanade; Charles River Basin; Buildings; Churches; Steeples; Stages; Hatch Memorial Shell; Boat houses; Union Boat House; Union Boat Club; Boats; Sailboats; People; Pedestrians; The Esplanade; Rivers; Charles River; Charles River Basin
  - Crowd awaiting a concert on The Esplanade, 1932; MS102.001.DO.00291; Globe Newspaper Co.
    Massachusetts; Boston (Mass.); The Esplanade; Buildings; Boat houses; Union Boat House; Stages; Concerts; People; Men; Women; The Esplanade
  - Boston skyline and the Charles River Basin, 1940; MS102.001.DO.00292; Scott, Rovere
    Massachusetts; Boston (Mass.); Charles River Basin; Buildings; Bridges; Longfellow Bridge; Rivers; Charles River; Charles River Basin; Boats; People
  - Johnson-Singleton house on Charter Street, 1850 -- 1890; MS102.001.DO.00293; Unknown
    Massachusetts; Boston (Mass.); North End (Mass.); Charter Street; Buildings; Dwellings; Houses
  - Concert at the Hatch Memorial Shell, June, 1943-06-01; MS102.001.DO.00294; Unknown
    Massachusetts; Boston (Mass.); The Esplanade; Stages; Hatch Memorial Shell; People; Orchestra; Concerts
  - House of the Good Samaritan at 4 and 6 McLean Street, 1870 -- 1890; MS102.001.DO.00296; Unknown
    Massachusetts; Boston (Mass.); Beacon Hill (Mass.); Chambers Street; McLean Street; Buildings; Dwellings; Houses; Churches; St. Joseph Catholic Church; Street-lighting; Fences; Church of St. Joseph
  - Fitchburg Railroad Company Passenger Depot, 1860 -- 1890; MS102.001.DO.00298; Unknown
    Massachusetts; Boston (Mass.); Causeway Street; Beverly Street; Buildings; Railroad stations; Electric lines, poles and towers; Clocks and watches; Horse-drawn vehicles; Carriages and carts; People; Fitchburg Railroad Company
  - Eastern Railroad Passenger Depot at 110 Causeway Street, 1889 -- 1893; MS102.001.DO.00299; Unknown
    Massachusetts; Boston (Mass.); Causeway Street; Canal Street; Buildings; Railroad stations; People; Pedestrians; Trolley buses; Clocks and watches; Eastern Railroad Company
  - Boston and Lowell, Eastern and Fitchburg Railroad Company Passenger Depots on Causeway Street, 1860 -- 1875; MS102.001.DO.00300; Ward, Joseph and Son
    Massachusetts; Boston (Mass.); Causeway Street; Buildings; Railroad stations; Horse-drawn vehicles; Wagons; Carriages and carts; Pedestrians; Clocks and watches; Trolley buses-tracks; Omnibuses-tracks; Boston and Lowell Railroad Company; Eastern Railroad Company; Fitchburg Railroad Company
  - Union Station, 1893 -- 1910; MS102.001.DO.00301; Unknown
    Massachusetts; Boston (Mass.); Causeway Street; Buildings; Railroad stations; Union Station; People; Men; Women; Trolley buses-tracks; Clocks and watches; Shepley, George F.; Rutan, Charles H.; Coolidge, Charles A.; Shepley, Rutan and Coolidge; Boston and Lowell Railroad Company; Boston and Maine Railroad Company
  - Heywood Brothers and Company at 81 Causeway Street, 1890; MS102.001.DO.00302; Unknown
    Massachusetts; Boston (Mass.); Causeway Street; Canal Street; Buildings; Commercial buildings; Businesses; Stores, retail; Furniture stores; Horse-drawn vehicles; Carriages and carts; Electric lines, poles and towers; Street-lighting; Signs and signboards; Hartwell, Henry W.; Swasey, Albert E. Jr.; Heywood, Henry; Heywood, George H.; Greenwood, A.M.; Morrill, Amos; Hill, Calvin H.; Walsh, John D.; Heywood Brothers and Company
  - Causeway Street, 1961-07-12; MS102.001.DO.00303; Unknown
    Massachusetts; Boston (Mass.); Causeway Street; Buildings; Elevated railroads; Automobiles; Pedestrians
  - Causeway Street, 1961-07-12; MS102.001.DO.00304; Unknown
    Massachusetts; Boston (Mass.); Causeway Street; Buildings; Commercial buildings; Businesses; Signs and signboards; Automobiles; Trucks, automobile; Pedestrians
  - Eastern Railroad Company Passenger Depot, 1850 -- 1893; MS102.001.DO.00305; Clark, William T.
    Massachusetts; Boston (Mass.); Causeway Street; Buildings; Railroad stations; Electric lines, poles and towers; Clocks and watches; People; Men; Trolley buses-tracks; Omnibuses-tracks; Eastern Railroad Company
  - Razing of Union Station, January, 1928-01-01; MS102.001.DO.00306; Egan, Arthur J
    Massachusetts; Boston (Mass.); Causeway Street; Haverhill Street; Demolition site; Buildings; Railroad stations; Union Station; People; Boston and Maine Railroad Company
  - Boston and Lowell Railroad Company and Eastern Railroad Company Passenger Depots, 1889 -- 1893; MS102.001.DO.00307; Unknown
    Massachusetts; Boston (Mass.); Causeway Street; Buildings; Railroad stations; People; Trolley buses; Horse-drawn vehicles; Carriages and carts; Clocks and watches; Boston and Lowell Railroad Company; Eastern Railroad Company
  - Fitchburg Railroad Company Passenger Depot, 1889 -- 1900; MS102.001.DO.00308; Unknown
    Massachusetts; Boston (Mass.); Causeway Street; Buildings; Railroad stations; Clocks and watches; Trolley buses; Street-lighting; People; Men; Fitchburg Railroad Company
  - Crowd in North Station, June, 1943-06-01; MS102.001.DO.00309; Unknown
    Massachusetts; Boston (Mass.); Causeway Street; Buildings; Railroad stations; North Station; People; Men; Women
  - Bulfinch Place, 1955; MS102.001.DO.00310; Neiley, Robert
    Massachusetts; Boston (Mass.); Beacon Hill (Mass.); Bulfinch Place; Bulfinch Street; Buildings; Hotels; Commercial buildings; Businesses; Restaurants, lunch rooms, etc.; Signs and signboards; Automobiles; Bowdoin Lunch; Argonne Hotel; St. Leon; Waterston Hotel
  - Bulfinch Street, 1957; MS102.001.DO.00311; Neiley, Robert
    Massachusetts; Boston (Mass.); Beacon Hill (Mass.); Bulfinch Street; Allston Street; Buildings; Dwellings; Houses; Automobiles; Fences; Commercial buildings; Office buildings; Streets; New England Telephone and Telegraph Company
  - Unidentified street in Beacon Hill, 1950; MS102.001.DO.00312; Neiley, Robert
    Massachusetts; Boston (Mass.); Beacon Hill (Mass.); Buildings; Automobiles; Streets
  - Unidentified street in Beacon Hill, 1950; MS102.001.DO.00313; Neiley, Robert
    Massachusetts; Boston (Mass.); Beacon Hill (Mass.); Buildings; Automobiles; Doors; Streets
  - Corner of Joy and Beacon Streets, 1950; MS102.001.DO.00314; Neiley, Robert
    Massachusetts; Boston (Mass.); Beacon Hill (Mass.); Beacon Street; Joy Street; Streets; Automobiles; Traffic signs and signals; Fire hydrants
  - Charles Street, Sullivan House, west side of Charles Street near corner of Beacon Streeet, n.d., MS102.001.DO.00315; Unknown
    Massachusetts; Boston (Mass.); Beacon Hill (Mass.); Charles Street; Beacon Street
  - Massachusetts Charitable Eye and Ear Infirmary at 176 Charles Street, 1870; MS102.001.DO.00316; Hawes, Josiah Johnson
    Massachusetts; Boston (Mass.); Beacon Hill (Mass.); Charles Street; Buildings; Infirmaries; Massachusetts Charitable Eye and Ear Infirmary; Fences; Trees; Reynolds, Dr. Edward; Jeffries, Dr. John; Massachusetts Charitable Eye and Ear Infirmary
  - Chauncy Street, 1860; MS102.001.DO.00318; Hawes, Josiah Johnson
    Massachusetts; Boston (Mass.); Washington Street Shopping District; Chauncy Street; Rowe Place; Buildings; Social and civic buildings; Churches; Rowe Street Baptist Church; Dwellings; Houses; Massachusetts Charitable Mechanics Association; Rowe Street Baptist Church
  - 20-28 Charles Street, 1974; MS102.001.DO.00319; Weaver, David
    Massachusetts; Boston (Mass.); Beacon Hill (Mass.); Charles Street; Buildings; Commercial buildings; Businesses; Real estate business; Taxicabs; Streets; Pedestrians; Dwellings; Dormitories; Olde Boston Reality, Inc.; Massachusetts General Hospital Freshman Trainee Dormitory/Lincolnshire Dormitory
  - Massachusetts General Hospital, 1875 -- 1898; MS102.001.DO.00320; Unknown
    Massachusetts; Boston (Mass.); Beacon Hill (Mass.); Blossom Street; Buildings; Hospitals; Massachusetts General Hospital; Trees; Massachusetts General Hospital
  - 20 Charles Street, 1973-01-14; MS102.001.DO.00321; Waid, C. Franklin
    Massachusetts; Boston (Mass.); Beacon Hill (Mass.); Charles Street; Buildings; Dwellings; Dormitories; Massachusetts General Hospital Freshman Trainee Dormitory/Lincolnshire Dormitory